{
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": 0,
            "question": "What do you want to submit?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "I want to submit GWAS data",
                    "next": { "type": "question", "id": 1 }
                },
                {
                    "label": "I want to submit both GWAS and PGS data",
                    "next": { "type": "question", "id": 101 }
                },
                {
                    "label": "I want to submit only PGS data",
                    "next": { "type": "question", "id": 11 }
                }
            ]},
        {
            "id": 1,
            "prevId": 0,
            "question": "Are these GWAS described in a published manuscript?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "Yes",
                    "next": { "type": "question", "id": 2 }
                },
                {
                    "label": "No",
                    "next": { "type": "question", "id": 3 }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "prevId": 1,
            "question": "Is the manuscript indexed in PubMed, i.e. has a PMID?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "Yes",
                    "next": { "type": "route", "path": "curation_queue" }
                },
                {
                    "label": "No",
                    "next": { "type": "route", "path": "form", "formType": 1, "formAnswer":  "No", "bowType": "GCP"}
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "prevId": 1,
            "question": "Are these GWAS described in a manuscript submitted or accepted for publication?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "Yes",
                    "next": { "type": "route", "path": "form", "formType": 2, "formAnswer":  "Yes", "bowType": "GCP"}
                },
                {
                    "label": "No",
                    "next": { "type": "question", "id": 4 }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "prevId": 3,
            "question": "Are these GWAS described in a manuscript hosted on a pre-print server?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "Yes",
                    "next": { "type": "route", "path": "form", "formType": 3, "formAnswer":  "Yes", "bowType": "GCP"}
                },
                {
                    "label": "No",
                    "next": { "type": "question", "id": 5 }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "prevId": 4,
            "question": "Are these GWAS described in a draft manuscript (not submitted anywhere)?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "Yes",
                    "next": { "type": "route", "path": "form", "formType": 4, "formAnswer":  "Yes", "bowType": "GCP"}
                },
                {
                    "label": "No",
                    "next": { "type": "route", "path": "form", "formType": 4, "formAnswer":  "No", "bowType": "GCP"}
                }
            ]
        },


        {
            "id": 11,
            "prevId": 0,
            "question": "Is the PGS published in a manuscript?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "Yes",
                    "next": { "type": "question", "id": 12}
                },
                {
                    "label": "No",
                    "next": { "type": "route", "path": "form", "formType": 2, "formAnswer":  "Yes", "bowType": "PCP" }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "prevId": 11,
            "question": "Does it have a PMID?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "Yes",
                    "next": { "type": "route", "path": "curation_queue"}
                },
                {
                    "label": "No",
                    "next": { "type": "route", "path": "form", "formType": 1, "formAnswer":  "No", "bowType": "PCP"}
                }
            ]
        },


        {
            "id": 101,
            "prevId": 0,
            "question": "Are the GWAS and PGS described in the same publication, preprint or manuscript?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "Yes",
                    "next": { "type": "question", "id": 102 }
                },
                {
                    "label": "No",
                    "next": { "type": "alert", "message": "Please make separate submissions for the GWAS and PGS" }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 102,
            "prevId": 101,
            "question": "Have you already made a GWAS submission for this preprint/publication?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "Yes",
                    "next": { "type": "question", "id": 103 }
                },
                {
                    "label": "No",
                    "next": { "type": "jump", "message": "Please make your GWAS submission first",
                        "jumpTo": 0,
                        "selectedOnJump": "I want to submit GWAS data"
                    }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 103,
            "prevId": 102,
            "question": "Do you know your GWAS Catalog Study Accession ID(s) - beginning GCST?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "Yes",
                    "next": { "type": "question", "id": 104 }
                },
                {
                    "label": "No",
                    "next": { "type": "alert", "message": "You can download a list of study accessions for your completed submission from the submission page:  https://www.ebi.ac.uk/gwas/deposition/submission/<your submission id>, using the “Download Study Accession” button in the top right corner." }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 104,
            "prevId": 103,
            "question": "Is your submission a preprint or Publication?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "Preprint/manuscript",
                    "next": { "type": "route", "path": "form", "formType": 2, "formAnswer":  "Yes", "bowType": "GCP" }
                },
                {
                    "label": "Publication",
                    "next": { "type": "route", "path": "curation_queue"}
                }
            ]
        },


        {
            "id": 999,
            "question": "All questions answered",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "label": "All Done!",
                    "next": { "type": "question", "id": 0 }
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
